

# CONTACT

- **\** 082 340 4002
- ☑ ian.terhaar1004@gmail.com
- Strand, Western Cape
- github.com/lanTerHaar
- in www.linkedin.com/in/iterhaar/

### **EDUCATION**

2022 - 2024

**Eduvos Private University** 

 Bachelor of Information Technology

2017 - 2021 Strand High School

Matric Certificate

# CODING LANGUAGE

- Java primary
- Kotlin
- SOL
- HTML
- CSS

#### **SKILLS**

- Fast learner
- Teamworking
- Leadership

## LANGUAGES

- English (Fluent)
- Afrikaans (Fluent)

# IAN TER HAAR

# SOFTWARE ENGINEER

### **PROFILE**

I am a 21-year-old ambitious student, currently studying Information Technology at the University of Eduvos. I matriculated in 2021 and I am excited to pursue my career in Software Development.

My key characteristics are a strong work ethic, professionalism and I am very conscientious. I pride myself in challenging work that produces good outcomes and results.

During my Grade 10 year as a student at High School Strand, I had the opportunity to travel alongside eleven other scholars to London and Europe where I was an exchange student at the Roeselare Exchange Scheme. During my stay in Europe, we were connecting with various groups of people in London, Paris and in Belgium. It was a very insightful experience, and I learned about connecting with people around the world.

### WORK EXPERIENCE

The Mom and Baby House

2024 - Present

E-commerce Product Photographer and SEO Copywriter

- Improved the visual appeal of the product catalog, resulting in increased customer engagement and sales.
- Successfully boosted website traffic through effective SEO techniques, leading to higher search engine rankings and visibility.

Hero Events

2023 - Present

Venue Bartender

- Successfully crafted and served a variety of cocktails and beverages tailored to the unique themes and audiences of diverse venues.
- Successfully managed high-volume service during peak events, ensuring efficient operations and positive customer experiences

Casa Del Sol

2022 - 2023

Cocktail Bartender

- Developed and executed a diverse range of signature cocktails, consistently receiving high praise from patrons.
- Managed inventory, ordering supplies, and controlling costs to maintain profitability while minimizing waste.

## **REFERENCE**

Mikayla van Dyk

The Mom and Baby House

Phone: 082 504 4221

Email: mikayla@babyhouse.co.za

Schalk Venter
Software Engineer

Phone: 074 815 1365

Email: Venterschalk@gmail.com